<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Joel Guerra</title>
    <link>http://joelguerra.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Joel Guerra</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 17:40:55 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://joelguerra.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How To: Replace an Accelerator Pedal Position Sensor</title>
      <link>http://joelguerra.com/cars/how-to-replace-an-accelerator-pedal-position-sensor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 17:40:55 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://joelguerra.com/cars/how-to-replace-an-accelerator-pedal-position-sensor/</guid>
      <description>You Should Know How To️: replace an accelerator pedal position sensor 2004 Honda Accord outside of a detail shop
This is my 2004 Accord. It has been my daily driver for 6 years. It has 285k miles. Everything works and it’s great — except that lately the throttle has been… weird. It starts jerky and doesn’t cruise at a consistent speed even if I am very smooth with my pedal input.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To: Restore Your Car’s Exterior Trim</title>
      <link>http://joelguerra.com/cars/how-to-restore-your-cars-exterior-trim/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 13:27:18 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://joelguerra.com/cars/how-to-restore-your-cars-exterior-trim/</guid>
      <description>Restore Your Car’s Exterior Trim I’m going to show you how to restore the lower plastic trim on this ‘99 Honda Prelude but the process will be the same on most cars.
Everyone knows that the Honda Prelude is one of humanity’s finest achievements. In terms of engineering, style and heritage it has few rivals — But sadly the last one rolled off the assembly line in 2001. Those of us who own one today have a moral obligation to maintain it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make a Stack Overflow Reputation Leader Board for Your Team With Python</title>
      <link>http://joelguerra.com/tech/make-a-stack-overflow-reputation-leader-board-for-your-team-with-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 17:37:26 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://joelguerra.com/tech/make-a-stack-overflow-reputation-leader-board-for-your-team-with-python/</guid>
      <description>Make a Stack Overflow Reputation Leader Board for your team with Python If you’re a developer or student you probably have a Stack Overflow account. If you’re as (overly) competitive as I am you probably compare your Stack Overflow reputation with your colleagues. If you’re a real weirdo you might even want a sort-able leader board to compare yourself against your friends, enemies, etc.
Well, look no further than this simple Python Flask application!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I Blasted Your Drug Deals on Twitter</title>
      <link>http://joelguerra.com/tech/why-i-blasted-your-drug-deals-on-twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 17:33:20 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://joelguerra.com/tech/why-i-blasted-your-drug-deals-on-twitter/</guid>
      <description>Why I Blasted Your “Drug” Deals on Twitter How it happened A couple of days ago Twitter user Mike Rundle tweeted a link for the endpoint to Venmo’s public API. I learned that Venmo’s public by default setting made the details of millions of Venmo transactions publicly available to anyone who cared to look. So I did what any software engineer would do and started digging through the data. I could see the names, Facebook profile pictures, payment types and “message” fields that users filled out when they made a transaction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To: SSH to Your Azure Linux Vms With Username and Password From Windows Linux or Mac</title>
      <link>http://joelguerra.com/tech/how-to-ssh-to-your-azure-linux-vms-with-username-and-password-from-windows-linux-or-mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 May 2018 13:27:18 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://joelguerra.com/tech/how-to-ssh-to-your-azure-linux-vms-with-username-and-password-from-windows-linux-or-mac/</guid>
      <description>How To: SSH to your Azure Linux VMs with username and password from Windows, Linux or Mac If you’re looking to generate SSH keys and use them to login to an Azure Linux VM then good on you because that’s the recommended and most secure method to access your VMs. It’s readily documented here in official documentation. However, I’ve seen people asking on forums how to simply connect to a Linux VM hosted in Azure via SSH with a username and password.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To: Embed Your Azure Web App Bot in Any Web Page</title>
      <link>http://joelguerra.com/tech/how-to-embed-your-azure-web-app-bot-in-any-web-page/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 May 2018 13:18:41 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://joelguerra.com/tech/how-to-embed-your-azure-web-app-bot-in-any-web-page/</guid>
      <description>How To: Embed your Azure web app bot in any web page Embedding an Azure bot in your web page is actually very simple but the Azure portal doesn’t make it obvious how to do this. The portal blade for bots is geared towards developers who are integrating bots into channels like Skype, Facebook Messenger, Slack, SMS, etc but I’ve seen several questions on Stack Overflow asking how to simply slap the bot on a web page - so here you go.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>