<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>/tech on Joel Guerra</title>
    <link>https://joelguerra.com/tech/</link>
    <description>Recent content in /tech on Joel Guerra</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 12:31:04 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://joelguerra.com/tech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Draw a Dick on the City of Bellevue’s “Report Gatherings” Map With Go</title>
      <link>https://joelguerra.com/tech/how-to-draw-a-dick-on-the-city-of-belleuve/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 12:31:04 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joelguerra.com/tech/how-to-draw-a-dick-on-the-city-of-belleuve/</guid>
      <description>The city of Bellevue, Washington recently debuted an online tool to allow residents to report “gatherings” or other violations of Governor Inslee’s “shelter in place” order. Bellevue Police Department plans to make a heat map to identify areas with high concentrations of violations. This guide will walk through how to reverse engineer an API and use Go’s standard library to send form data. We’ll use the “report a gathering” application as the example API.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s Build a Computer Together — the Martin files</title>
      <link>https://joelguerra.com/tech/lets-build-a-computer-together/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2019 00:38:29 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joelguerra.com/tech/lets-build-a-computer-together/</guid>
      <description>In this edition of “the Martin files” I cobbled together Martin’s gigantic twitter thread (with his permission) documenting a complete gaming PC build. This is the highest budget thread to date! Have fun!
🖥️ LET’S BUILD A COMPUTER TOGETHER! 🖥️
I’m building a PC for work &amp;amp; games and I’m going to share my experience for folks who are thinking about it. Even on my 8th-9th build, I make mistakes and learn new things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>API Basics With Postman — the Martin files</title>
      <link>https://joelguerra.com/tech/api-basics-with-postman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 00:15:44 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joelguerra.com/tech/api-basics-with-postman/</guid>
      <description>This week I’m stealing all of Martin Castro&amp;rsquo;s hardwork from Twitter (with his permission) to bring you his guide on using Postman to consume APIs. This is a great way to test an API before you starting writing code. The rest of this post is straight from Martin’s thread:
👽 LEARNING THE HARD WAY: API basics with Postman 👽
I am going to use Github’s Noop Challenge — Hexbot to teach y’all about one of biggest tools in my API toolbelt, Postman.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unboxing Hardware: Photon Particle Wifi — the Martin files</title>
      <link>https://joelguerra.com/tech/unboxing-hardware-photon-particle-wifi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 00:21:50 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joelguerra.com/tech/unboxing-hardware-photon-particle-wifi/</guid>
      <description>Here’s another edition of Martin Castro live tweeting hardware and me collecting it all into a single digestible blog post. The rest of this post is direct from Martin’s finger tips here. Enjoy!
Let’s check out this beginner / intermediate microcontroller kit! I am working on a TOP SECRET project with @joelatwar and @CodeSpent and I thought I’d take a couple minutes to talk about this lil’ IoT device and unbox it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started With Microcontrollers — the Martin files</title>
      <link>https://joelguerra.com/tech/getting-started-with-microcontrollers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2019 00:08:14 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joelguerra.com/tech/getting-started-with-microcontrollers/</guid>
      <description>My buddy Martin Castro likes to live tweet hardware projects. When he’s done you have a detailed step-by-step guide that anyone can follow along. However, since it’s a Twitter thread it is quickly lost to time. “The Martin Files” is my attempt to capture this content (with his permission) so others can find, read and learn from it in the future. The rest of this article (including the images) will be verbatim from his Twitter thread:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make a Stack Overflow Reputation Leader Board for Your Team With Python</title>
      <link>https://joelguerra.com/tech/make-a-stack-overflow-reputation-leader-board-for-your-team-with-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 17:37:26 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joelguerra.com/tech/make-a-stack-overflow-reputation-leader-board-for-your-team-with-python/</guid>
      <description>If you’re a developer or student you probably have a Stack Overflow account. If you’re as (overly) competitive as I am you probably compare your Stack Overflow reputation with your colleagues. If you’re a real weirdo you might even want a sort-able leader board to compare yourself against your friends, enemies, etc.
Well, look no further than this simple Python Flask application!
Screenshot of example leaderboard
Here is an example of this website in action using myself and some friends: http://sampleleaderboard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I Blasted Your Drug Deals on Twitter</title>
      <link>https://joelguerra.com/tech/why-i-blasted-your-drug-deals-on-twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 17:33:20 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joelguerra.com/tech/why-i-blasted-your-drug-deals-on-twitter/</guid>
      <description>How it happened A couple of days ago Twitter user Mike Rundle tweeted a link for the endpoint to Venmo’s public API. I learned that Venmo’s public by default setting made the details of millions of Venmo transactions publicly available to anyone who cared to look. So I did what any software engineer would do and started digging through the data. I could see the names, Facebook profile pictures, payment types and “message” fields that users filled out when they made a transaction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To: SSH to Your Azure Linux VMs With Username and Password From Windows, Linux or Mac</title>
      <link>https://joelguerra.com/tech/how-to-ssh-to-your-azure-linux-vms-with-username-and-password-from-windows-linux-or-mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 May 2018 13:27:18 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joelguerra.com/tech/how-to-ssh-to-your-azure-linux-vms-with-username-and-password-from-windows-linux-or-mac/</guid>
      <description>If you’re looking to generate SSH keys and use them to login to an Azure Linux VM then good on you because that’s the recommended and most secure method to access your VMs. It’s readily documented here in official documentation. However, I’ve seen people asking on forums how to simply connect to a Linux VM hosted in Azure via SSH with a username and password. If that’s you then I assume you have a good reason (like this VM will generally not have ports open to the internet or this is a proof of concept) and this post will detail how.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To: Embed Your Azure Web App Bot in Any Web Page</title>
      <link>https://joelguerra.com/tech/how-to-embed-your-azure-web-app-bot-in-any-web-page/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 May 2018 13:18:41 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joelguerra.com/tech/how-to-embed-your-azure-web-app-bot-in-any-web-page/</guid>
      <description>Embedding an Azure bot in your web page is actually very simple but the Azure portal doesn’t make it obvious how to do this. The portal blade for bots is geared towards developers who are integrating bots into channels like Skype, Facebook Messenger, Slack, SMS, etc but I’ve seen several questions on Stack Overflow asking how to simply slap the bot on a web page - so here you go.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>