<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>python on Joel Guerra</title>
    <link>https://joelguerra.com/tags/python/</link>
    <description>Recent content in python on Joel Guerra</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 17:37:26 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://joelguerra.com/tags/python/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Make a Stack Overflow Reputation Leader Board for Your Team With Python</title>
      <link>https://joelguerra.com/tech/make-a-stack-overflow-reputation-leader-board-for-your-team-with-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 17:37:26 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joelguerra.com/tech/make-a-stack-overflow-reputation-leader-board-for-your-team-with-python/</guid>
      <description>If you’re a developer or student you probably have a Stack Overflow account. If you’re as (overly) competitive as I am you probably compare your Stack Overflow reputation with your colleagues. If you’re a real weirdo you might even want a sort-able leader board to compare yourself against your friends, enemies, etc.
Well, look no further than this simple Python Flask application!
Screenshot of example leaderboard
Here is an example of this website in action using myself and some friends: http://sampleleaderboard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I Blasted Your Drug Deals on Twitter</title>
      <link>https://joelguerra.com/tech/why-i-blasted-your-drug-deals-on-twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 17:33:20 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joelguerra.com/tech/why-i-blasted-your-drug-deals-on-twitter/</guid>
      <description>How it happened A couple of days ago Twitter user Mike Rundle tweeted a link for the endpoint to Venmo’s public API. I learned that Venmo’s public by default setting made the details of millions of Venmo transactions publicly available to anyone who cared to look. So I did what any software engineer would do and started digging through the data. I could see the names, Facebook profile pictures, payment types and “message” fields that users filled out when they made a transaction.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>